（雷の音）
＜昔々あるところに
それはそれは凶悪で→
Once upon a time, in a land far far away,
there was a barbaric, ruthless, and defiant,
残忍で傍若無人で
人を人とも思わぬ→
悪魔のような男がおりました＞
demon-like bastard who thought
nothing of his fellow man.
（ベル坊）ビエエエ～！
（男鹿）ボジャゲボおお～。
（爆発音）
（ベル坊）…ビ　ダブ。
アイ…。
（男鹿）な　何だ。
突然　泣き出しやがって…。
What?
Why the hell are you crying all of a sudden?
（ヒルダ）…眠いので
ぐずっておられるのだ。
He is sleepy and irritable.
それくらい坊っちゃまの親なら
察しろ。
If you're really his parent,
then you should realize this.
眠いなら勝手に
寝りゃいいだろ～が。
グ～ビ～。
If he's tired, he should just sleep!
そんな理屈が通れば
誰も子育てに苦労はせぬ。
If that line of thinking worked, it would
not be such a struggle to raise a child.
早く坊っちゃまを寝かせろ。
さもないと…。
Now hurry and put the master to sleep.
ウ～ダ…。
If you do not...
イヤヤ　イヤイヤヤ…。
ビエエエ～。
（爆発音）
ボヤボヘ～！
アイ…アイ…ア。
あ…。
お？
フ～フ～フ～。
（アランドロン）＜これは　ひょんな事から
赤ん坊を→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
育てる事になった
不良高校生の物語。ただし→
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
その赤ん坊は
普通の赤ん坊ではなく→
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
魔王の子だったのです＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
There Is 1 Second Before the Demon Lord's Floods Burst Forth
海…か。
The ocean?
え～何これ…夢？
What is this? A dream?
…ああ　夢だな絶対。あれだ
目が覚めると→
Yeah, definitely a dream.
That's it. I'm going to wake up, and
Baby Beel will have wet my bed again.
ベル坊が横で　おねしょしてるとか
そんなオチだ。
That old joke.
ったく　夜泣きの次は
おねしょかっての。
Man... First he cries all
night, now he wets the bed?
目覚めろオレ。そして
シーツを取り替え→
Wake up, me!
Then after changing the
sheets, go to sleep again!
二度寝しろ　オレ～！
You hear me, me?
ん…。
ぷ～ふ～。
え～？何これ。
目が覚めたか？
The hell...?
Awake?
あ…。
よい朝だな。坊っちゃまも→
A fine morning, yes?
Master is peeing quite splendidly.
豪快に　おもらししておられる。
おもらし？
Peeing?
案ずるな　汚いものではない。
むしろ→
Worry not.
It is not unclean.
On the contrary, it is urine imbued with
holy magical powers one should give thanks for...
神聖な魔力を秘めた
ありがたい　お小水だ。
毎年この時期に迎える排尿期は
魔界でも→
The great urination comes
each year around this time,
and in the Demon World it is a seasonal attraction.
風物詩でな。街１つ飲み込んだ
その後には→
After a city is drowned in the flood,
the amount of fertile land increases.
肥沃な大地が広がる。フフ…。
人間を滅ぼす為の第一歩だな。
笑えね～よ！
The first step in destroying humanity, yes?
This ain't a joke!
おねしょで人類滅亡って。おめ～もいつまで　のんきに寝てんだコラ！
Humanity is being peed to extinction?
And how long are you gonna just sleep there?
（アランドロン）相変わらず素晴らしい→
Your peeing is incredible as always, Master!
お小水ですな　坊っちゃま～。
アイ。
（アランドロン）
どんぶらこっこ　どんぶらこ→
Floating... Floating... Floating...
どんぶらこっこ　どんぶら
ストップ。
Float and stop!
（古市）おい
どこ連れて来てんだよ。
Hey, where are you taking me?
こ　これは…ゴボゴボ…。
Wait, this is...
いや～この　お小水を
是非　古市様にも見て頂きたくて。
I simply wished to show Furuichi-sama
this splendid urination!
懐かしいですな～。魔界にいた頃はよく娘と→
It brings back memories, yes...
Back in the Demon World,
my daughter and I would often amuse
ourselves floating downurine...
お小水下りに興じたものですぞ。
…プハ！川下りかよ。ゴボ　助けて。
You go tubing down uriine?!
Help me!
おい　いい加減この洪水
何とかしろ！
Hey. Do something about this flood already.
まったく　人間というのは…。
仕方あるまい。
Humans, honestly...
So be it.
…エイ。
何だこりゃ。
What the heck?
おお何と猛々しい。
お小水を少しの間→
Ooh, how fierce!
It is an item from the Demon World which
temporarily sends his pee into an alternate dimension.
異空間に飛ばしておく事ができる
魔界グッズ。
その名も「とばすにょ～」。
やたら語尾かわいいけど→
It is called "Peebeegone".
The end sounds cutsey. But
it's just a joke, right?
ダジャレっすよね。
ダジャレでも何でもいい→
Joke, no joke, it doesn't matter.
これで街も沈まずに済む。
いや　沈むぞ。
This way, the city can
stay above water level.
No, it will flood.
（古市・男鹿）え？
異空間とはいえ→
Although it is an alternate
dimension, it is not infinite.
容量は無限ではない　せいぜい
もって２～３時間だろう。
It will last only 2 to 3 hours.
何？
新しいのに取り替えれば
いいんじゃね～の。
What?!
Can't we just replace it with a new one?
予備はない。
何だと～。
There's no spare.
What?!
…まったく往生際の悪いヤツらだ。
You people just can't accept your fate.
この際　どの街から沈めるか
考えればよかろう。
You should be spending this time
deciding which city to drown.
よ～し　お前
もう　しゃべるな！
Alrighty then! You, shut the hell up!
いいか　今は一時的に
沈静化しているが　依然→
Okay, he's calmed down for now, but the
Baby Beel dam is gonna burst at any time!
ベル坊ダムは決壊寸前　予断を
許さぬ状況だ。
We cannot let down our guard.
幸い今日は　うちに誰もいねえ。
今のうちに→
Thankfully, no one is home today at my place.
Right now we need to come up with a plan.
どうすればいいか
知恵をひきちぎれ！
We've got rip off our brains!
（古市）知恵をふりしぼれ…な。
ひきちぎれ！
You mean, wrack our brains!
Rip them off!
えっと…何度も言うが
オレを巻き込むなって。
お前だけが頼りだ。
Uh, whatever you say, but
don't involve me in it.
But you're the only one I can count on!
何か　いいアイデア出たか？
出てね～し　出す気もね～よ。
You got a good idea, right?
No, I don't!
And I don't wanna come up with one!
出せよ！出そうよ。早く出さね～と
出ちまうぜ。
ダブ。
You'd better come up with one!
Come up with one, or its comin' out, got it?
（古市）うまくね～よ　ムカつくな。
何だ　そのどや顔。
That's not even close to funny!
What's with that face?
バカヤロー古市！てめえ　このまま３時間後に→
Furuichi, you idiot!
You're okay letting Japan
sink into an ocean of pee?
日本が尿に沈んでもいいのか！
うるせ～よ！てめ～が
親なんだから自分で…。
Shut it!
You're the damn parent, so you do something!
[TV]おもらしの赤ちゃんの大洪水
まあ大変～。
My baby pees so much, I don't know what to do!
（男鹿・古市）ん？
[TV]どんなおしっこも→
No leaks for 10 hours, no matter the amount!
漏らさず１０時間！幻のオムツ
「オムティ」で赤ちゃんも安心。→
With the mystical diapers "Daipies",
your baby will be safe and sound!
もう洪水なんて怖くない！
オムティ　これだ！
I'm not scared of leaks anymore!
Daipies!
That's it!
[TV]次のニュースです。先ほど銀行に
強盗が押し入り…。
The news continues.
There has just been an armed bank robbery...
古市！家の事は任せた。
おいコラ待て。任せたって…→
Furuichi, you handle cleaning up the house!
Wait, what do you mean...
What should I do with
everything soaked like this?
ど～すんの　この水浸し！
元通りにしてくれ！ヨロシク。
Fix it back up like it was!
Countin' on ya!
ってか　普通のオムツで
どうにかできる問題じゃね～だろ。
And wait... Normal diapers
aren't gonna work, obviously.
待ってろよベル坊　どんな大洪水も
漏らさねえからな。
ダ～！
Just you wait, Baby Beel!
They said no leaks, no matter the amount!
…ったく。相当テンパってんな
あいつ。
Sheesh...
He's such a simpleton.
ってか　これ
オレが貸した漫画じゃん。
手伝うのか？
Wait, this is manga I lent him!
You're going to help him?
（古市）そりゃまあ　少しくらいはね
友達っスから。
Well, a little bit.
'Cause he's a friend, you know.
《お…オレ今　かっこよくね？》
Ooh, I was totally cool back there!
ヒルダさんこそ…いくら
仕事とはいえ　あんなアホと→
Even if it's your job, it must be difficult
raising a baby with that idiot... Right, Hilda?
子育てなんて大変でしょ？
((そ～なんですよ。→
That's so right!
あのクサれ　どアホは。
わかります～))
He's such a total nincompoop, you know?
((困ったヤツですね～))
What are we to do with him?
《これでヒルダさんの心を
ガッチリ》
And with that, Hilda-san's
heart will be mine!
…仕事？
Job?
みくびるなよ。
（古市）え？
Do not degenerate it!
私の坊っちゃまに対する
忠誠を愚弄する気か？
You dare to make a mockery
of my devotion to my master?
侍女悪魔とは　その名の通り
お仕えする　その人の為だけに→
A demon maidservant is just as the name says:
A demon born with the sole
purpose of serving her master.
生まれてくる悪魔だ…。
仕えるべき人も→
The person we serve, and the place we serve
at, are all decided prior to our birth.
仕えるべき場所も　生まれる前から
決まっている…。わかるか？
Do you understand?
ベルゼ坊っちゃまに
お仕えする以外→
My existence itself has no other
meaning than serving Master Beel!
私の存在理由など　ないのだ。
仕事などと…。
It is no mere job!
チッ…あの男を追う！
（古市）あ！待って。
I'm going after him!
Wait!
（アクババ）グア。
《私としたことが…人間相手に
何を話してる。→
What am I saying to some human?
全ては　坊っちゃまの意のままに。
そう決めたではないか…》
Everything according to my master's will.
That is how it is, yes?
（アクババ）グア～！
（古市）待って下さいよ～。
Please, wait, Hilda-san!
ヒルダさ～ん！
（夏目）
いらっしゃいま…。あ～
男鹿ちゃんじゃん　どうしたの？
Welcom...
Oh, it's Oga-chan!
What's up?
いや　幻のオムツを…ってか
あんた誰？
I'm looking for mystical diapers...
And who are you?
ああ　「オムティ」の事？
あれチビッターって→
Oh, you mean diapies?
Those got all popular on the internet
after people posted about them on Chirper.
ネットの掲示板で　有名に
なっちゃってさ～。
今　全然　在庫ないんだよね。
ゲ！ねえのかよ。
So we don't have any in stock right now.
You ain't got any?
オムツだったら　他にも
いいのあるからさ。→
If you're looking for diapers,
we have plenty of other brands.
色々　見ていってよ。
Take a look at the different kinds.
う～ん。
ダブ。
この間は凄かったね　男鹿ちゃん。
Smileypants
You were quite impressive
back then, Oga-chan.
何が？
ダブ。
About what?
（夏目）神崎君　全治１ヵ月だって。
ま　これから→
I hear Kanzaki-kun is going
to take a month to heal fully.
But after that, things are gonna get busy.
忙しくなるよ～。石矢魔東邦神姫の
１人を　やっちゃった訳だからね。
Since you did in one of Ishiyama's TKKH.
はあ？
知らないの？うちの学校の→
Huh?
You didn't know?
Those are the 4 great powers at our school.
４大勢力だよ。東条　邦枝　神崎→
Tojo, Kunieda, Kanzaki, and Himekawa....
姫川…その頭文字をとって
石矢魔東邦神姫。
By taking the first letter of each of
their names, you make the Ishiyama TKKH.
どうだ　ベル坊？
ダブ。
How about this one, Baby Beel?
だよな～。幻のオムツじゃ
ね～もんな。
Yeah, no kidding.
These sure ain't mystical diapers to me.
フ…やれやれ。
Sheesh...
今度のは　ど～だ。
ダ…ブ。
How about these?
（善光）おとなしくしろ！
Stay calm!
（龍崎）さもねえと命はねえぞ！
（悲鳴）
If you don't, you're dead meat!
（大山）…フン。
（古市）ハアハア…ヒルダさん。
Hilda-san!
ん　何だ？
ア！イ…。
What?
（三ノ宮）さて　人質は
これだけか…。
This is all the hostages we got?
ダブ。アイ　アイ…。
《ど～ゆ～事！》
What the hell is going on?!
According to the report we've just received,
[TV]たった今　入ったニュースに
よりますと…→
先ほど
石矢魔銀行を襲った強盗団が→
the armed suspects who
robbed Ishiyama Bank escaped
and are holed up in a nearby drug
store! They've taken hostages!
逃走中　近くのドラッグストアに
人質をとり→
立て籠ったとのことです。→
We bring you a live report...
現場からの中継です。
オウ？
[TV]え～　こちら現場です。→
We're reporting live from the scene.
Ishiyama Drug
情報によりますと　店内には
高校生２人とコスプレ女性→
According to the information we have,
inside the store were 2 high school students,
one cosplaying female, and
what is believed to be a baby.
それに赤ちゃんもいる模様です。
ん～　ワァオ！
（警官）中に入らないで！
あ～　男鹿ちゃん達
巻き込まれちゃったか…。
Oh, my... Oga-chan and the
gang are caught up inside...
（三ノ宮）
ちっ！サツに通報されたか…→
Damn it! We're surrounded by cops!
ったく　お前が
モタモタしてたせいだぞ！
This is your fault for
takin' your sweet time!
Well, as long as we have hostages,
they can't make their move so easy.
まあ　人質がいるお陰で　向こうも
簡単には手出しできねえよな。→
ヘヘヘ…。
あんたら
あたいらに逆らおうなんて→
Okay, people. Don't go thinking anything
stupid like puttin' up a fight.
バカなこと考えるんじゃないよ。
（龍崎）
強盗　窃盗　器物破損　前科６犯！
Armed robbery, grand
larceny, property damage...
Six crimes in all!
（善光）
ありとあらゆる悪事に手を染めた
犯罪グループ！
We're the criminal group that
does every kind of evil deed!
大山！
Oyama!
Ryuzaki!
龍崎！
Zenkou!
善光！
Sannomiya!
三ノ宮！そうさ　その名も…。
And that makes our name:
ｏｒｚ三！
orz3!
Speed groveling!
スライディング土下座！！
Right!
そう！スライディング土下座！
Speed... grovel!
Wait! No, you dumbass!
って違うわ　ボケー！！
ダブー。
おっ！？
Anyway, you're our hostages until
we're well on our way to Hong Kong!
とにかく　お前ら俺達が無事に香港
に高飛びするまで人質だからな。
妙なマネすると　ぶっ放すぞ。
Get out of line and we'll
blast you full of holes.
シャレになんねえ…前科６犯って
根っからの悪人じゃないか。
This is serious!
6 different crimes? These
guys are bad to the bone!
ん？悪人…？
ダ？
Did you say bad?
Gotta think of a way to escape...
逃げる方法を考えろ
石矢魔の智将　古市貴之！
Think, Furuichi Takayuki, the one
they call the strategist of Ishiyama!
って　おい！男鹿～！！
Hey! What are you doing, Oga?
You idiot... If they're such bad dudes,
I can dump Baby Beel onto them!
バカヤロー　こんだけ悪い奴らならベル坊を押し付けられるだろ。
はあぁぁ？
What's with you?
何だ　てめえ！
動くんじゃないよ！
I thought we said not to move.
So how bad are you?
お前ら　どのくらい悪いんだ？
はあ？
Huh?
強盗なんだろ？
You're robbers right? I asked
ya just how evil you are.
どのぐらい悪いことやってんのか
聞かせろってんだよ。
You sure got a big mouth on you, huh?
てめえ　何偉そうに言ってんだ？
ああっ？
What're you getting worked
up about some kid for?
お前ら　ガキ相手に
何熱くなってんだ？→
ほう…いい面構えだ。度胸といい
俺の若い頃に似てるぜ。
I like the look in your eyes.
You got guts. Reminds me
of when I was younger.
Fine then! We'll tell
you, for your own future!
いいだろう
将来のために聞かせてやるぜ。
Yes, please do. I'm sure you're all amazing.
ああ　頼む。すごいヤツをな。
ダー。
Oyama!
大山！
フン！あたいが
アンタぐらいの頃は→
When I was your age, I was quite the rebel.
ずいぶんとヤンチャしたものさ。
学校中の窓ガラスを　こんなふうに
片っ端からメチャメチャに割ってさ！
I took all the windows in the school
and shattered 'em like this!
（ガチャーン！）
ひいっ！！
フフッ…そして　そのガラスの
破片でこうやって…。
And then, with the shards of glass, I...
I'd get rid of extra hairs, like this...
ムダ毛の処理をしたものさ。
ん？
は！？
フフフ…。
それって悪か？
Is that... evil?
正直　微妙…。
Honestly speaking... Kind of weak.
Are you an idiot?
バカか　てめえ！ムダ毛処理を自慢
する銀行強盗が　どこにいんだよ！
We don't need any bank robbers bragging
about their follicle maintenance!
（大山）ぐはっ！
ようしゃねえ！！
No mercy!
龍崎！
Ryuzaki!
Back in my juvenile delinquent days,
there wasn't anyone who could touch me!
オウ！不良時代の武勇伝なら
俺にかなうヤツは　いねえぜ！
Why, you ask? Because I'm from the bowels
of delinquency, Ishiyama High School!
なんつったって俺は
あの不良の巣窟→
石矢魔高校の出身だからな！
Oh! I'm also from Ishiyama.
おおっ！俺も石矢魔だ！
ダーブー！
マジか！？道理で凶悪そうな
ツラしてやがると思ったぜ。
Really? No wonder I thought
your face looked bad-ass.
How's Ishiyama doin' lately?
どうだ　最近の石矢魔は？
俺らの時は　タネキントリオって
四天王がいてよ。
In my time, the Big Four
was the Tanekin Trio.
四天王なのにトリオ？
The Big Four was a trio?
いやいや　高見沢　根本　金田一
鳥岡の４人の頭文字をとって→
No, see...
Takamizawa, Nemoto, Kindaichi, Torioka...
If you take the first parts of their
names, you get "TaNeKin Torio"
タネキントリオって
呼ばれてたんだけどな。
この金田一ってのが
高校生のくせに→
And that Kindaichi guy,
despite being in high school,
すんげ～ギラギラ脂ぎったヤツで
ついたあだ名が…。
was always so showy and greased up...
He got the nickname...
Tellin' old stories? Don't
go gettin' carried away!
懐かし話で　ひとり勝手に
盛り上がってんじゃねえ～！！
（龍崎）ぐはっ！
Zenkou!
善光～！
チッ！どいつもこいつも
昔の自慢話か？情けねえ…。
Each and every one of you
is all about the past...
Pitiful.
Listen up. I'm a thief
that specializes in metal.
いいか　俺は金属専門の泥棒だ。
I steal things like fences and manhole
covers and sell them for cash.
フェンス盗んだり　マンホール
盗んだりして　金に換えるのよ。
Just a bit before, I did me quite a job.
この前は　でっかい仕事を
ひとつやってな→
I stole an entire steel tower!
鉄塔１本　まるごと盗んだぜ。
Steel tower?
鉄塔？
One of the towers disappeared by the
river, right? That was my doing.
河原の鉄塔が消えた事件が
あったろ？あれは俺の仕業だ。
悪い　それやったの　俺。
ダブ！
Sorry, but actually that was me.
えっ？
なあ　こいつらひょっとして
悪として全然ダメなんじゃねえか。
Hey, do you think they might
actually really fail at evil?
Enough! You guys, stay put!
もういいっ！！
てめえらは　ひっこんでろ！
銀行強盗は
どうやるか知ってるか？
You know how you go and rob a bank?
I'll teach you.
教えてやる。銀行に入った瞬間
逃げまどう奴らに銃をぶっ放し→
The second you enter the bank you
shove a gun through the window,
And you threaten them to
give you money like this!
金をつめろと脅す！
こうやってな！
（銃声）
キャーッ！！
ヘヘヘ…。
ダブー！
善光！どうだ　外の様子は？
Zenkou, how's it look outside?
Not much activity!
（善光）特に動きはないっス。
アー！
お　おい　ベル坊！
Hey, Baby Beel!
ん？何だ　こいつ！
What is with this kid?
アーッ！
Baby Beel!
ベル坊！
（大山）動くな！
Don't move!
（龍崎）お前ら　動くんじゃねえよ！
（三ノ宮）このっ！離れろ！！
I told you not to move, you!
Get off!
ちょうどいい。この赤ん坊は
俺が預からせてもらおう。
何だと？
Fine, perfect.
I'll be takin' this baby.
What?!
赤ん坊が人質なら　サツも
うかつに手出しはできねえ。
With a baby as a hostage, the cops
ain't gonna do anything stupid.
片手で抱えれば　邪魔にも
ならねえし抵抗されることもねえ。
I can carry 'im with one hand,
so he won't get in the way.
And he can't fight back.
考えてみれば　こんな都合のいい
人質はねえってもんだ。ヘヘヘ…。
Now that I think about it, this
is the best possible hostage!
男鹿　やったじゃねえか！
Oga, you did it!
Even if you don't ask this
guy, he's gonna take him away!
こっちから　お願いしなくても
向こうから預かってくれるって！
あ　ああ…そうだな。
Right... Yeah...
このまま　あいつらがベル坊を
香港に連れてってくれれば→
If he really takes Baby
Beel to Hong Kong with him,
日本は　沈まねえってことだ。
すげえ！男鹿にしては頭いいな！
Japan will be saved from the flood!
Wow... Oga, for you, that's good thinking!
Well, duh!
ったりめえだ！
ダーッ！…ヒッ！
（男鹿・古市）うわっ！
びぇえええっ～！
((え～ん　え～ん…))
((いい子ですから
もう泣かないでくださいまし))
Be a good boy and don't cry anymore, okay?
((え～ん　え～ん…))
（大魔王）
((つ～か　うちのガキどもは
みんな天邪鬼だからねえ。→
All my kids are little hellspawns...
言うこと聞いてたらキリねえよ))
((はあ…))
Give in to one of their demands,
and they'll never let up!
I see.
（大魔王）
((ま　肩の力抜いて
母親になったつもりで頼むわ))
Well, just relax. I'm countin'
on you becoming his mother.
Yes, Great Demon Lord.
((はい…大魔王様))
アイーッ…。
な　何なんだ　この赤ん坊は？
What the hell is this baby?
魔王の親となるからには
いろいろと契約が必要だ。
There are many contracts that are needed for
you to become the parent of the Demon Lord.
Do you have that conviction?
貴様に　その覚悟はあるか？
魔王の…親？
Parent of the Demon Lord?
人間界を滅ぼすため
坊っちゃまの触媒となり→
In order to destroy humanity, your role is to
become a catalyst to draw out the master's power.
魔力を引き出す役目を負う。
都市をなぎ払い　国を破壊し
人間を残らず滅ぼす手伝いをする。
Mow down cities, destroy entire nations...
Help extinguish all remaining
traces of humanity.
それが魔王の親の役目だ。
That is the role of the Demon Lord's parent.
面白えじゃねえか。
ここから逃げられるなら→
Sounds interesting!
If I get out of here, I'll be the
Demon Lord's parent or whatever!
魔王の親にでも何にでも
なってやるよ。
ボ　ボス　ヤバイっすよ　なんか。
その女も普通じゃないっすよ。
B-Boss, I think this might be dangerous!
That woman ain't normal!
マジでそんな赤ん坊
（善光）
連れてく気っすか？
うるせえ　黙ってろ！！
You're seriously gonna
take that baby with you?
I said shut it, you!
こんな赤ん坊　用がなくなりゃ
途中で捨てりゃいいだろ！
When I ain't got any more use
for him, I'll just ditch him!
では　望み通り
香港まで連れて行ってやろう。
Then I will take you to Hong
Kong, just as you wish.
アクババ！
Akubaba!
グエエエッ！
ひいいいっ！
ヘッ…ヘヘッ　ヘヘヘ…面白れえ。
いくぞ　お前ら！
ちょっと待て。
Interesting! Let's go, people!
Hold it a sec.
なっ！？てめえ！！
Why, you...
やっぱ　お前らだけで行け。
I think you should go all by yourselves.
No holding back for robbers either!
強盗にも容赦ねえ…。
ひいいっ！
うううっ…。
坊っちゃま？
Master?
あうっ　あっあっ…！
坊っちゃま！！
Master!
ベル坊！
Baby Beel!
早い…！
Fast...
ったく　もう決壊かよ。
３時間は早ぇな。
It broke already?
Three hours sure fly by...
Do something, would you? Your supposed
to act like his mother, right?
お前なんとかしろよ。
母親代わりなんだろ？
I'm countin on you becoming his mother.
（大魔王）
((母親になったつもりで頼むわ))
《大魔王様…》
Great Demon Lord...
あ～あ　せっかく日本を
救えるはずだったのにな。
グエ！
Aww... I thought I'd finally saved Japan.
つかまれ。海とやらまで飛ぶぞ。
Grab on. We'll fly to the ocean.
ダーッ！
グエ～！
Shouldn't you just have
done this from the start?
つ～か…最初っから　こ～すりゃ
よかったんじゃねえの？
黙れ　落とすぞ。
Silence. I'll push you off.
《大魔王様…私には
この男が計れません》
Great Demon Lord... I do
not understand this man.
However, it may be too early
to come to a conclusion.
《ただ　まだ結論を出すには
早すぎる…かもしれません》
We're home!
（男鹿父）ただいま～！
Tatsumi, we brought you...
辰巳　お土産…。
オウ？
Um...
えっと…誰？
Who are you?
Himekawa, one of Ishiyama's TKKH,
is not just strong, he's crazy rich!
How rich is he?
Commoners like us can't even fathom it.
Like, he only takes one bite from
the best part of a watermelon.
And then he throws the rest away! Like that.
On the next Beelzebub:
There is Nothing Money Can't Buy!
Don't waste food!